<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Culmyca 18</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">564937600532605</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb564937600532605</string>
    <string name="content_head">Its Latin root literature/literature (derived itself from litter-a: letter or handwriting) was used to refer to all written accounts, </string>
    <string name="click_here_to_continue"><u>Click Here to Continue</u></string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>>

    <!--<string name="content_head">Its Latin root literature/literature (derived itself from litter-a: letter or handwriting) was used to refer to all written accounts, </string>-->
    <string name="dummy">Its Latin root literature/literature (derived itself from litter-a:Its Latin root literature/literature (derived itself from litter-a:Its Latin root literature/literature (derived itself from litter-a:Its Latin root literature/literature (derived itself from litter-a:</string>
    <string name="rangritidata">"Don’t DO Fashion. Be Fashion”. Get ready to experience the world of elegance and beauty; the world of ethnics, with Fashion Parade. If you have the fire in you, this is the right place to be."</string>
    <string name="starnightdata">"Footfall of 3000+, over 50,000 watts of music, Stars performing live on stage and a string of passionate music lovers in the crowd. A lifetime experience that you cannot afford to miss."</string>
    <string name="mrmsculmycadata">"As they say “Beauty with brain is an absolutely deadly combination”, we believe: “A chivalrous knight is equally lethal”. So join in and prove your mettle to get hold of the most coveted title of the fiesta."</string>
    <string name="hassrathdata">"Is there a Kapil Sharma in you? Or is it Ellen Degeneres? Whoever it is. Get ready to put it upfront at HassRath-The Laughter Chariot. The stage is open for any kind of comedy. Language barrier is a thing of past, Comedy is what we ask for."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_brixx">BrixxActivity</string>
    <string name="aboutymca">The YMCA University of Science and Technology, Faridabad erstwhile YMCA Institute Of Engineering, was established as a joint venture of the National Council of YMCAs of India, Govt of Haryana, and the Central Agencies for Development Aid, Bonn, Germany.YMCAUST has been awarded \'AAA+\' by the Career360 Magazine in the year 2013, 2014 and 2015. YMCA University has also been accrediated with \'A\' grade by NAAC. Our University has been mandated to affiliate 50+ B.Tech and B.Ed institutions.</string>
    <string name="xunbao_about">Xunbao is a mind boggling online cryptic quest designed to put your cognitive abilities to test. It is a multi-level contest where you will be given cues which can be hidden anywhere on the internet, just about anywhere your wits may let you. Let the rolling of brain race with every passion of minute and zero in on the answers using the given cues to get your stakes and adrenaline higher.
Rules
1. Xunbao is an online event which you can play on the Culmyca App 2018
2.(more rules about no of players and how many questions have to be answered and what type of questions)</string>
    <string name="aboutEc">Elements Culmyca, the annual inter college cultech festival of YMCAUST has grown on to become one of the most popular college festivals of NCR. With 1000+ participating students, 40+ participating colleges and an expected footfall of over 10000, ELEMENTS CULMYCA 18 guarantees to be a sure hit The upcoming \'Kalakaars\' painting the entire college in the colours of their vivacity, the gaming freaks, the coding addicts. They are all a part of the same institution, busy doing what they do best.</string>
</resources>
